firstinterstatebank.com 2010-06-07

# First Interstate Bank - Privacy Statement

## FIRST INTERSTATE BANK

## PRIVACY POLICY FOR INDIVIDUALS

**Our Commitment**. Protecting your financial privacy is of utmost importance to First Interstate Bank. For many years now, we have maintained standards and procedures designed to prevent misuse of your financial information. We promise to maintain the confidentiality of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Our Board of Directors has adopted this Privacy Policy so that you will understand what information we collect and how we use it. 

**Nonpublic Personal Information We Collect**. We collect nonpublic personal information about you from the following sources: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms 
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates or others 
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency 

“Nonpublic personal information” is nonpublic information about you that we may obtain in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. This could include information such as account balances, payment history or overdraft history.” 

We collect and retain certain information about you for the following reasons: 

  * To protect your account and to identify you when we conduct transactions with you; 
  * When the information will help us in administering your accounts and services; 
  * To provide you with products and services that will best assist you or to help us understand your financial needs as we design or improve our products and services; and 
  * To comply with certain laws and regulations that apply to us. 

**Information We Disclose**. We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about our customers or former customers to anyone, except as permitted by law. 

Affiliates. Our “affiliates” include First Interstate BancSystem, Inc. and Crytech. We are permitted under law to share information about our experiences or transactions with you or your account with our affiliates. We do not share information about you or your accounts that we receive from consumer reporting agencies. 

Third Parties. Many times it is necessary to utilize other companies that provide services necessary to your banking relationship with First Interstate Bank. We are permitted under law to disclose nonpublic personal information about you to “nonaffiliated third parties,” that is, third parties that are not members of our corporate family, in certain circumstances. These companies act on our behalf when they provide services and are not authorized to use the information for any other purposes. For example, we may disclose nonpublic personal information about you to third parties that provide data processing services, print your checks, provide credit insurance products or provide technical assistance with our software programs. We may provide your name and address to companies that mail information to you about our own products and services. We do not share medical information that we may obtain in insurance applications or claims to anyone, except for the purposes you have authorized. We do not sell or share customer information to unrelated third parties to use for their own purposes. 

We may disclose the following information to companies that perform services on our behalf or to other financial institutions with which we have a joint marketing agreement. We maintain contractual confidentiality agreements with these third party service providers assuring that our customer information may not be shared with any other party or used for any other purposes than those contracted with us. 

  * Information we receive from you on an application or other forms, such as your name, address, social security number, assets and income; 
  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or others, such as your account balance, overdraft history, payment history, parties to transactions and credit card usage; 
  * Information we receive from a consumer reporting agency, such as your creditworthiness and credit history or your handling of a checking account. 

We may also provide information: 

  * When you authorize us to release information; 
  * To consumer reporting agencies; 
  * To comply with a law, regulation, court order or subpoena; 
  * To verify the existence of your account and general information about the condition of your account for a merchant or other financial institution; 
  * In response to an inquiry about whether a check you have written on an account will clear; 
  * To local, state and federal authorities if we believe a crime may have been committed involving your account; 
  * To our independent auditors, consultants or attorneys and to agencies that regulate us. 
  * To other parties when it is necessary or helpful in completing a transaction you initiate, including other financial institutions and networks involved in processing your transactions; 

**Our Security Procedures**. We also take steps to safeguard customer information. We restrict access to your personal and account information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We train our employees about the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of customer information. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information. 

**Maintaining Accurate Information**. We continually strive to maintain complete and accurate information about you and your accounts. If you ever believe that our records contain inaccurate or incomplete information about you, please let us know immediately. If we report any inaccurate information about your accounts(s) to a consumer reporting agency, please send a written notice describing the specific inaccuracy(ies) to us at: First Interstate Bank, Operations, PO Box 30918, Billings, MT 59116-0918. We’ll correct any inaccuracies as quickly as possible. 

**Policy Changes**. We reserve the right to change this policy from time to time, but we will not do so without first notifying you of any change. 

We value your business and look forward to providing you with banking services for many years to come. If you ever have questions or concerns about the integrity of your account information, please do not hesitate to call or visit your local First Interstate branch. 

Print Statement Back to Disclosures
